# VHISYHNU VIMILAN

### MY PROFILE

Hi there! I'm Vhisyhnu and I have around 4 years of web and software development experience. I love working with people to do things bigger than I could accomplish alone. A quick learner in a working environment while able to meet targets and deadlines with good precision.



#### RELEVANT SKILLS

#### FRAMEWORK

- Angular14
- AngularJS
- ASP.Net (.Net

Framework & .Net Core) Typescript

Laravel

#### DATABASE LANGUAGES

- VB
- C#
- HTML & CSS
- Javascript &

- jQuery
- PHP

#### MSSQL

- MYSQL
- Firebase

DEVELOPMENT

• Agile Scrum

- - RxJS
    - Linux OS

TOOLS

& LIBRARY

Postman API

• GIT & Bitbucket

- JIRA
- AzureDevops
- Pandas
- Docker

# CONTACT INFORMATION

- +6011-27605409
- vhisyhnu97@gmail.com
- LinkedIn: Vhisyhnu Vimilan

#### EDUCATION

#### Universiti Tenaga Nasional (UNITEN)

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE (SOFTWARE ENGINEER) (HONS.)

MAY 2017 TO FEBRUARY 2019

# SOFT SKILLS

- Extremely Organized
- Fast Leaner
- Team Work
- Leadership
- Self-motivated
- Able to communicate in 3 Languages (English, Malay, Tamil,

Beginner Level Mandarin)

- Logical Thinker
- Time Management
- Adaptability
- Providing and accepting feedback

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Software Engineer**

VIEWPOINT RESEARCH CORPORATION SDN. BHD.

#### **JANUARY 2020 TO PRESENT**

- Web and Desktop application development (Full Stack)
- Worked in an Agile team of .Net developers for a fast-paced software development firm.
- Responsible for application software programming (C#, VB.Net, Angular14, AngularJS, MSSQL)
- Actively participate in Agile Software Development
- Enhanced the application's features to effectively fix the bugs and optimize the overall performance, reliability and efficiency
- Conduct research for new technology/ methodology.
- Work as a part of team to discuss, plan and implement new features and enhancements.

#### **Junior Web Developer**

IT WONDERS WEB DESIGN

#### FEBRUARY 2019 TO DECEMBER 2019

- Full stack web programmer (Laravel, Python, MySql)
- Planning and implementing tasks given by stakeholder of project following the due date given.
- Communicated with clients to implement Web Services
- Supported testing and engineering processes.
- Confirmed that completed software met client requirements.
- Completed maintenance on existing programs.
- Worked closely with product team on scope of future projects and innovations.